coursekart.com 2012-03-25

# CourseKart- Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy 

**Collection and Use of Your Personal Information**

We only collect information that is absolutely necessary in order to serve you.  
We collect information from our users at several different points, including but not limited to the following:

**Information You Provide To Us**

Before you can use the Services (as defined in the User Agreement) on the Site, we ask that you register with us and provide us your personal information including Name, e-mail address, Password etc. We store this information so that you can access our site securely.  
We collect information about our users' utilization and navigation of our Site. This information helps us to design our Site to better suit our users' needs. We also use your IP address to help diagnose ��� problems with our server and to administer our Site, to gather broad ��� demographic information and to help identify you.  
Like many websites, we use cookies at our Site. We only use cookies for the smooth operation of the web application.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time, our Site may request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is ��� completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include but is not ��� limited to contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).  
We may also send out email newsletter (with an option to unsubscribe) to maintain contact with our users and subscribers.

### Information sharing

CourseKart only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of CourseKart in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of CourseKart, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If CourseKart becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  
We restrict access to personal information to CourseKart employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Restrictions on Disclosing Information to Third Parties**

We are not in the business of selling or renting your personally identifiable information to others. We do not reveal personally identifiable information about you to third parties for their independent use unless: (1) the information is provided to complete a transaction for you; (2) the information is provided to comply with the law, enforce our User Agreement or other agreements we have with you, or to protect our rights, property or safety, or the rights, property or safety of others; (3) the information is provided to our agents, vendors or service providers who perform functions on our behalf.

**Security Measures to Protect Information**

To help protect the privacy of data you transmit through use of this Site, WE use industry-standard security standards and procedures to help prevent unauthorized access to confidential information about you. In addition, we train our employees about the importance of confidentiality and maintaining the security of your information. We ��� commit to taking appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce our employee�s privacy responsibilities. It is also important for you to help protect against unauthorized access by signing off of our Site each time you finish using it.

**Inapplicability of Privacy Policies of Any Linked Sites or Other Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy only addresses our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites or linked ads, although we encourage you to read any applicable privacy policies of such parties or websites.

**Conditions of Use, Notices and Changes to Our Privacy Statement**

By using this Site and any of our services or products you agree to the terms and conditions in this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement. In the event of any conflict between the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, then the User Agreement shall control. If you do not agree to any of these terms and conditions you should not use this Site and any of our services or products.

As our business changes from time to time, this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement are expected to change. We reserve the right to ��� amend the Privacy Policy and User Agreement at any time, for any reason, without notice to you, other than the posting of the amended ��� Privacy Policy and/or User Agreement to the Site. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and terms and conditions, but you should check the Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy ��� in effect and any changes that may have been made to it. The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and User Agreement in effect at the most recent time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices.

We monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to the web service. Use of our web site constitutes consent to such monitoring and auditing. Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on this web site are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution.

**Questions Regarding Our Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at� :� **privacypolicy@coursekart.com**
